Register of the William John Green Papers, 1911-1982
Hoover Institution Archives
- U.S. Special Technical and Economic Mission to Burma, 1949-1953 (Box 23-24:)
  - "Program of Agricultural Extension Training Conference for Deputy Directors of Agriculture with Outlines of Discussions and Demonstrations,", 1952 (Folder 24: 15)
  - "Observation on Rubber Situation in Burma," report by W. J. Green, 1952 (Folder 24: 16)
  - Stem-Fao-Un agricultural workers meeting, 1952 (Folder 24: 17)
  - "Quarterly Report on Economic Progress in Burma,", 1952 (Folder 24: 18)
  - "Classification of Land and Water Resources," by Richard R. Covell, land capability specialist, 1952 (Folder 24: 19)
  - "Suggestions for Fresh-Water Fisheries Research in the Burma Department of Agriculture," by Verne E. Davison, fresh-water biologist, 1952 (Folder 24: 20)
  - "Evaluation of the Experimental Procedure Used in Burma to Determine the Response of Rice to Fertilizers," report, 1952 (Folder 24: 21)
  - "Interview with Mr. William J. Green, Head of Agricultural Division, TSA,", September 19, 1952 (Folder 24: 22)
  - Future of agriculture in Burma, press release and clippings, 1952 (Folder 24: 23)
  - "The Agriculture Program in Burma," closing report, 1953 (Folder 24: 24)
  - "Bill's Far East Letters, 1950-1952," by William J. Green, circa 1953 (Folder 24: 25)
- Servicio Agricola Interamericano (SAI) in Bolivia files, 1948-1956 (Box 25:)
  Consists of programs, memoranda, reports, printed matter, clippings, memoirs and interview
  - Santa Cruz: A Socioeconomic Study of the Area in Bolivia, by Olen E. Leonard, 1948 (Folder 25: 1)
  - U.S. - Bolivia Technical Cooperation Agreement, 1951-1955 (Folder 25: 2)
  - "Bolivia- Office of Foreign Affairs (OFAR) Mission," inspection report, 1952 (Folder 25: 3)
  - "Ground Water Conditions in the La Loma Area, North of Santa Cruz, Bolivia," by R. M. Leggette, consulting ground water geologist, 1952 (Folder 25: 4)
  - Livestock improvement, 1952-1955 (Folder 25: 5)
  - Personnel, 1953-1955 (Folder 25: 6)
  - Report of Santa Cruz Area Development Mission, Foreign Operations Administration, Washington D.C., 1954 (Folder 25: 7)
  - Campo, Publicacion mensual del banco agricola de Bolivia, no. 92, 1954 (Folder 25: 8)
  - Experiment stations, 1954-1955 (Folder 25: 9)
  - Extension work, 1954-1955 (Folder 25: 10)
  - Wheat production and fertilizers, 1954-1955 (Folder 25: 11)
  - Supervised agricultural credit, 1955 (Folder 25: 12)
  - Tractor project and machinery pools, 1955 (Folder 25: 13)
  - Farm boys and girls clubs and farm youth exchange, 1955 (Folder 25: 14)
  - "Servicio Agricola Interamericano, Ministerio de Agricultura, Bolivia, informe annual, Julio 1, 1954-Junio 30, 1955," (Folder 25: 15)
  - Accomplishments of SAI and the future of agriculture, 1955 (Folder 25: 16)
  - "Bill's Latin American Letters. Second Series, 1953-1955," by William J. Green, circa 1956 (Folder 25: 17)
- Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction (JCRR), Taipei, Taiwan, China, 1950-1978 (Box 26-31:)
  Consists of programs,progress and study reports, minutes, writings, brochures, and memoirs.
  - General Report on the JCRR, 1950-1958 (Folder 26: 1-5)
  - General Report on the JCRR, 1959-1966 (Folder 27: 1-4)
  - General Report on the JCRR, 1967-1976 (Folder 28: 1-5)
  - Land Reform in Taiwan, 1958 (Folder 28: 6)
  - "Agriculture Extension Division JCRR Staff Conference,", 1959-1962 (Folder 28: 7)
  - "Agriculture Extension Division JCRR Staff Conference,", 1959-1962 (contd.) (Folder 29: 1-3)
  - "Monthly Report,", 1959-1962 (Folder 29: 4)
  - Farmers' Associations in Pictures, circa 1960 (Folder 29: 5)
  - Intensive Village Improvement in Taiwan, 1960 (Folder 29: 6)
  - 4-H Club (Head, Heart, Hand, and Health) brochures, circa 1960 (Folder 29: 7)
  - Home Economics Extension in the Republic of China, 1961 (Folder 29: 8)
  - "A Study on the Effects of the Population Trend on Economic Development in Taiwan,", 1961 (Folder 29: 9)
  - "Statistical Data about Kinmen as of December 31, 1961" (Folder 29: 10)
  - Organization and operations report, 1961-1962 (Folder 29: 11)
  - "Program and Plan of Work,", 1962 (Folder 29: 12)
  - Rice production report, 1962 (Folder 29: 13)
  - Reports on achievement by consultant W. T. Myers, 1962 (Folder 29: 14)
  - Study reports, 1962 (Folder 29: 15)
  - Agriculture in Taiwan, by the Taiwan Provincial Department of Agriculture and Forestry, 1962 (Folder 29: 16)
  - "Agricultural Development Potentials of Taiwan," prepared by JCRR, 1962 (Folder 29: 17)
  - "William Green Retires," JCRR Newsreel, 1962 (Folder 29: 18)
  - "Taiwan Topics; Talks and Papers," by W. J. Green, 1964 (Folder 30: 1)
  - "Bill's Far East Letters. Second Series," by W. J. Green, circa 1964 (Folder 30: 2)
  - Preparation for extension work, 1965 (Folder 30: 3)
  - Agricultural Development in Free China, by T. H. Shen, chairman Chinese-United States JCRRA, 1965 (Folder 30: 4)
  - "Agricultural Progress and Family Situation in Taiwan," and other study reports by Anna Hwang Chin Ming Li, 1968 (Folder 30: 5)
  - The Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction, 1948-1968, Taipei, circa 1968 (Folder 30: 6)
  - The Asian Vegetable Research and Development Center, Annual Report, 1972-1973,, Taiwan, Republic of China, 1974, circa 1968 (Folder 31: 1)
  - JCRR and Agricultural Development in Taiwan, 1948-1978,, Thirteen Anniversary Publication, Taiwan, Republic of China (Folder 31: 2)